funcheap.com 2019-09-15

# Privacy Policy

It is Funcheap’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Funcheap collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Funcheap’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Funcheap’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Funcheap may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Funcheap also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments and entering contests. Funcheap only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Funcheap choose to interact with Funcheap in ways that require Funcheap to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Funcheap gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Funcheap does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Funcheap may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Funcheap may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Funcheap does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Funcheap discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Funcheap’s behalf or to provide services available at Funcheap’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Funcheap’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Funcheap will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone, unless the user has opted in to have their information shared. For example, if you enter a contest and choose to receive notifications about the results of the contest, we may provide your information to the promoter of the contest for the purpose of them notifying you of the results and in some cases to be signed up for their email list as determined through an opt/in out tick box on the page where you entered the contest. If you have opted in to receive information from one of our partners, we will do our best to ensure that they provide a clear and easy way to unsubscribe, but cannot be held liable for ways that their privacy policy differs from that of Funcheap. In addition, if you win a contest, we may provide your contact information to the promoter for the purposes of arranging the prize to be delivered to you or picked up. Funcheap also periodically will allow third party companies sponsor dedicated emails to our email list, however the emails are sent directly from Funcheap and your personal information is not shared with the third party except in the case where you have opted in to have your information shared. These third party companies who sponsor contests and content on Funcheap have their own respective privacy policies if you choose to provide them with your information on the third party website. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Funcheap discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Funcheap believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Funcheap, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Funcheap website or email list and have supplied your email address, Funcheap may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Funcheap and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Funcheap takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Funcheap uses cookies to help Funcheap identify and track visitors, their usage of Funcheap website, and their website access preferences. Funcheap visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Funcheap’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Funcheap’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Funcheap, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Funcheap goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Funcheap may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy and that there may be changes to the policy

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Funcheap and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Funcheap may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Funcheap’s sole discretion. Funcheap encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
